Hello?
(Sheldon:)Penny, this is not a good time.
(Sheldon:)No, I told you, you're not prepared
for the Sanctum of Burning Souls.
(Sheldon:)You need to be in a group of at least five
and one should be a level 35 healer.
No, I can't log on and help you.
(Sheldon:)We'll talk when I get home.
(Sheldon:)I'm not getting the computing time,
am I?
(Leslie:)Dumb-ass.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you have to do something
about Penny.
(Sheldon:)She is interfering with my sleep.
She is interfering with my work.
(Sheldon:)If I had another significant aspect
of my life...
(Sheldon:)...I'm sure she'd be interfering
with that too.
Why should I do something?
You introduced her to online gaming.
(Sheldon:)Well, yes, but you're the one
who said hello to her when she moved in.
(Sheldon:)If you'd simply restrained yourself,
none of this would be happening.
- Well, just tell her to leave you alone.
- I did. I told her. I texted her.